oh hey ladies and gentlemen didn't you
see you there you scared me uh welcome
back today we've got none other than uh
xcia whistleblower John kiraku what's
going on John hey good to be back
Chris uh I'm always happy to see you um
I just wanted to read off some of the
titles look you you have published so
many books in in such a short amount of
time you have The Reluctant spy my
secret life of the CIA war on terror uh
a convenient the convenient terrorist
Abu Zeda and the weird Wonderland of
America's Secret Wars you have doing
time like a spy how the CIA taught me
how to survive and thrive in prison
which again you blew the whistle on the
whole torture program and all you got
was a lousy t-shirt and a and a prison
time not not so great um no also you got
these new ones which the cia's inside gu
Guide to the Iran crisis maybe we could
talk about that a little bit um how to
disappear and live off the grid a CIA
insiders guy uh lying and lied to
detection a CIA Insider
guide uh and what the latest is
surveillance and surveillance detection
a c CIA insiders guide uh you just you
must have a callus on your rear end from
writing so much and you know I have
another one coming out in a couple of
weeks I decided to do something
completely different so I wrote one
called Remains of the Day The Ultimate
Guide to Washington DC's historic
cemeteries interesting something
different can you give us a little
inside about what that
ever since I was a little kid I've been
fascinated by cemeteries I find them to
be incredibly relaxing I like the uh the
architecture the symbolism and and
mostly you know everybody's got a story
you don't have to be famous um to be
interesting and uh God knows dozens of
books have been written about Arlington
Cemetery and it it shocked me to learn
that nobody had ever written a book
about Washington DC's cemeteries so I
did I love it I love it they are they're
quite peaceful it's a nice place to go
like an easy riter go drop some acid and
you know relax with the prostitutes um
but so last time we talked we were
talking about the um your pardon and
everything and I just wrote this article
I was trying to tell people hey this guy
deserves a pardon thank you you know I
think manfor got a pardon all these
these monkeys got a pardon what's is it
dead in the water what's the what's the
latest on that there's actually a story
behind it you know I I had some really
great support When Donald Trump was
President uh to pardon me and um I had
hired a I had hired a republican
lobbyist who really didn't do anything
to help but I also struck up a
friendship with Tucker Carlson and
Tucker carried the water for me and
um and so I applied for the pardon
and I knew I was close right I could
feel it I could feel feel like I was
close and then Tucker call Tucker called
me on the final day of the uh Trump
Administration can I swear on this
podcast oh [__] yeah oh good okay so he
calls me and he's like are you sitting
down I said what what are you hearing he
goes he's going to Pardon little [__]
Wayne and I said what he goes yeah
little [__] Wayne is going to get a
pardon
today and I said what about my pardon
and he said there's a story he said let
me call you right back he calls me back
about two hours later he said it's not
going to happen he said you were on the
list with Julian Assange and Ed Snowden
the three of you and Mitch McConnell got
wind of it and McConnell called Trump
and and said if you pardon Assange and
Snowden Mitch McConnell doesn't know who
the heck I am if you pardon Assange and
Snowden he said you will lose every
Republican in the Senate and you'll be
convicted on the impeachment uh uh
counts
so he just dropped all of us now why I
had to be tied with Assange and Snowden
I don't know I mean I my own personal
belief is they deserve
pardons but uh but we all three got
dropped and then that was the end of it
so I've reapplied under Biden now I've
got great amazing support in the Greek
American
community and uh you know I'm just going
to hope for the best we'll see what
happens yeah I we'll always be in your
corner rooting for you like you said
Julian Assange also another one of these
guys who deserves to be pardoned we
we'll see I find it interesting where
you have uh Tucker Carlson doing this
180 and actually doing some pretty good
stuff even from the perspective of a
leftist doing some good stuff but then
the rest of the time talking about
aliens and Jesus and stuff and so I'm
like okay that's strange I'll take what
I strange tell I went on Fox a couple of
days ago um only because they're they're
like wholly supportive of a pardon and
they're wholly supportive of of Julian
Assange now part of that is is because
they believe that Assange helped to give
us Donald Trump and we can agree or
disagree about that it doesn't really
make any difference but I'll go on Fox
just like I'll go on CNN or MSNBC If the
message is right and it always surprises
me at um how many people will unfriend
me on social media if I've gone on Fox
it's it's
nuts it's like why why why do you put
yourself in a corner where you're only
going to associate with the people who
agree with you on all the issues that
doesn't make any sense to
me and you know what let me tell
you if
I so I am
single and um and I'm I'm looking so I'm
on these apps like so many other people
are and I meet this woman and she is
absolutely stunning and not just
stunning smart she has a master's degree
in archaeology and she did a dig in
Greece and a dig in in Israel and she's
in a
very senior
position um in
government at at at a deputy assistant
secretary position right so we start
texting we start calling and I said
listen I I want to be transparent and
upfront um you should know a little bit
about me and she said oh I know who you
are Mr kiraku I never used my last name
but she said I know who you are Mr kako
I said okay great well if it's okay with
you then it's great with me can't wait
to go out we go out to dinner have a
fantastic time I ask her out a second
time we go out the second time fantastic
time and then I say to her hey there's
this little town outside Washington
called uh Shepherdstown West Virginia I
said it's a it's got like art galleries
and boutiques and bars and restaurants
let's go on Saturday and we'll walk
around town we'll have lunch and you
know hang out she said
great I pick her up 10:00 on a Saturday
morning as soon as she gets in my my car
I can tell something's
wrong so I said are you okay what's
wrong nothing nothing she goes nothing
everything's fine I said well clearly
something's bothering you what is it and
she
says well I have doubts about your
progress
credentials and I said excuse me I said
I went to prison for my Progressive
credentials and then she
says I saw a YouTube video of you last
night in which you quoted Ronald
Reagan and I said all right I know what
quote you're talking
about I said Ronald Reagan was right
when he said that government is the
problem it's not the solution to the
problem but the rest of that quote was I
said even a broken clock is right twice
a
day and she says I just need to process
this I need to think about it I'm like
okay whatever we go to Shepherd's toown
have a nice time but she's kind of cool
for the for the day finally around
around 3:00 it starts to rain and it's
raining kind of heavily so I said look
why don't we just get in the car we'll
go back to DC so we get in the car and I
don't like to sit on my phone when I'm
in the car so I take my phone out of my
back pocket I put it in the cup
holder and we're driving and I get a
text message it
goes so I I
look and I thought [__] it was a text
message from soer
Carlson and it
said it said hey buddy haven't heard
from you in a while let me know if
you're free for a beer so I kind of I
give her the side eye like this just to
see you know has she
noticed and she's like that John yeah
looking at the text message so I pretend
I didn't notice and then she goes do you
know Tucker
Carlson and I said yes and he's a l l
guy you don't have to agree with him I
disagree with him on 95% of the issues
but he's a nice guy and she says take me
home right now and don't ever call me
again oh so I did but that's Washington
in 2024 that's isn't that on par with
your tagline from your show the red team
blue team everybody needs to have this
tribalistic it's either red team blue
team no in between no nuance
that's it can you imagine just as
recently as the
1990s Republican and Democratic members
of Congress used to live together in
group houses on Capitol Hill play poker
together on Fridays go to church
together on
Sundays now they would just to soon kill
each
other yeah yeah that's the level of the
discourse but the Democratic party is is
in horrible horrible shape terrible the
neoliberal they have lost their minds
and it's led by this old mummified uh
guy walking around who's barely sentient
he doesn't know where he is half the
time can't find a chair to sit down and
all wandering off the stage um and and
then beyond that just um imperialist
genocidal kind of yeah foreign policy
even Kissinger said I see no aim in the
current U uh United States foreign
policy even Kissinger was like you guys
are doing it wrong you know it's funny
that you say that because just last
night I had a similar convers ation in
which I told a friend of mine that as
much of a genocidal
Maniac as Kissinger
was he at least had goals in foreign
policy you know you can disagree about
what he did in Chile and Cyprus and
Vietnam and a dozen other places around
the world but you knew what his policy
was you knew what the goal was and real
politique was
real it was only because of Kissinger
that Nixon went to China it was only
because of Kissinger that that Nixon and
bnv were able to negotiate
deant and you're right there there's no
discernable policy from this
Administration or the last one for that
matter and even the one before Barack
Obama I mean it was it was just kind of
a standard run-of-the-mill neoliberal
war-loving you know lead from behind and
still pretend to be the leader kind of
kind of traditional
policy nothing bold nothing special
certainly nothing advocating peace in
any
way no and yeah I mean kinger didn't
advocate for peace necessarily but at
the same time the the end result was at
least and not that I'm for imperialism
at all but at least the end goal was to
strengthen the United States but in in
the case of everything Bush it's been
actually to create more enemies abroad
that's right it seems or maybe that's uh
on accident or whatever but yeah it just
seems like there's not anything clear
now you we're steeped in Ukraine and
everything like this and and look at the
Drone program just as one
example um you know so many of us
thought this was a fluke of the George W
Bush Administration and it wasn't the
Drone program is probably the single
biggest the single most important
recruiting tool for terrorist groups
that
exists I can't tell you how
many Al-Qaeda
Fighters I captured or helped to capture
who told exactly the same thing that
they had no beef with the American
government until our drones killed their
dads their brothers their uncles their
Imam Blew Up The Village blew up the
school blew up the hospital
and then they were compelled to take up
arms against
us well you know in George W Bush's last
month as president he killed 24 people
with drones and in Barack Obama's last
month as president he killed more than
400 people with
drones so you know what kind of policy
is that it's a policy of
failure and what do we get out of it I
mean what you can say that the war on
terror was some vague idea going and
getting Vengeance and all these people
but were we trying to get oil out of
Iraq or what right just stealing the
resource was that that's really the goal
I guess um so I did I did want to ask
you
about go ahead yeah I I did want to ask
you because you know we got right now
there's conflict in Georgia uh that
seems to be instigated without any
credibility we don't know for sure but
it seems like the CIA is behind this
color Revolution that's going on in
Georgia um Ukraine is obviously being
backed by the United States pretty
heavily uh and Naval now navali was an
interesting character and I wanted to
get your take on it because he went to
Yale and and you were you were actually
the one who was recruited from a
university he went to Yale which is like
one of the places that they are known to
have CIA recruitment programs what's
your take on naoli what's your take on
Georgia and these kind of things
well let's talk about Georgia first I'm
fascinated by what's happening in
Georgia um but I think that the bottom
line there is actually quite clear um
the bottom line is that our policy
whether it's stated or not is to create
as many problems for the Russians
especially on their borders as we
possibly can
so you know we're we're pumping tens of
billions of dollars into Ukraine uh
we're not going to stop you know that
joke that we'll fight to the last
Ukrainian that's actually not a joke
it's the
policy right we will fight to the last
Ukrainian um so we've got that we've got
the policy of of encirclement you know
the the Baltic countries are all in NATO
Poland's in NATO Ukraine is de facto
NATO and
um and why not stir up trouble in
Georgia you know whether it's over this
stupid uh foreign agent
registration copycat law or just
stirring you know poking The Hornet's
Nest to to draw the Russians in I'm
surprised we're only doing it in Georgia
I'm surprised we're not also doing it in
Armenia you know the Russians have tried
hard to to walk a tight rope between the
Armenians and the and the
aaries we don't give a [__] about the
aaries I'm surprised we haven't jumped
in with both feet on the side of the
Armenians if only I mean it's not
because we even care about the Armenians
if only to to upset the Russians so to
me that's that's sort of the the easy
issue now naali I don't have the
foggiest idea if naali was working for
the CIA or the FBI or if they even ever
approached him I have no idea but I can
speculate and my speculation would be
that at the very very least he had been
approached probably more than once
probably by the FBI because it's the FBI
that does that kind of thing on us soil
they're jealously protective of their
Turf when it comes to their bureaucratic
uh fights with the
CIA the FBI would have had to been a a
gaggle of fools to not Approach naali at
at Yale and I I would bet money that
they did right even if he had told them
to go [__]
themselves they would have been remiss
in their in their jobs had they not
approached
him um I would have approached him but
you're right and you know I want to
point something out too cuz I get this
question a lot you know the story of how
I uh joined the CIA I was recruited in
graduate school my my grad school
adviser was actually undercover as a
grad school adviser looking for people
who might fit into the CIA culture he
recruited me into the CIA the truth was
I was getting married 6 weeks after
gradu I had no job lined up I wanted to
see the world I wanted to be involved in
public service so it was kind of a a
nice match for a
while
um that's different now it's different
since passage in 1993 of the um of the
Equal Employment Opportunity Act you
can't you can't just do that because
what was happening is all these these
white male Eastern liberal undercover
people were recruiting other
white male Eastern liberal you know grad
students and
so you know I remember 1993 when it like
dawned on them at the agency that that
we had no African-Americans or women the
women were all in support positions it's
like nobody's black nobody's Hispanic
nobody's Asian like what are we doing
it's 1993 For Heaven's Sake so that
changed and when that Chang
changed the CIA became more overt in its
campus
uh I'm going to use the word operations
in air quotes so instead of being
undercover as a grad school adviser
instead of being undercover as a you
know an international Affairs Professor
they just did it all
overtly and so what they would do is
take people in the last three years of
their careers and put them in these
academic positions um intelligence
fellow right at universities All Over
America hundreds of them so if you're
senior intelligence service you've been
a station Chief or you're a gs-15 former
station Chief uh and you're getting
ready to retire in two or three years
well wouldn't you like a cushy position
I have a friend for example wanted to
retire to the Midwest to his hometown
and um he had been a Soviet
um focused case officer during the Cold
War and so they said okay why don't we
send you to this major university in the
midwest with 50,000 students uh why
don't you teach a course
on Espionage in Soviet literature that
was one that they helped him make up uh
you can do one on um the history of
Soviet operations in the United States
from like 1950 to
1980 and there was some other history
class that he did so he would teach
these three
courses he did it for three years and
then he retired You Know Rich and fat
and happy and then they brought in the
next would be CIA retiree well multiply
that by 150 universities all across the
country what better recruitment tool
could you possibly have I mean to be
able to stand up there on on stage in a
lecture hall that's holding three or
four or 500 people and say I spent the
last 32 years at the
CIA and I'm going to teach you about X Y
and Z there there's going to be a a line
of 20 20 people at the end of the
semester who are going to want to know
if you can help them apply if you can
write them a letter of
recommendation so instead of having it
all be undercover you're doing it
overtly in front of everybody's face and
you're even more successful that
way incredible incredible that that's
the the base morality of college
students that that many of them would
stand up and say I want to sign up to
travel the world and learn meet
interesting people and learn to kill
them um yes what what has the CIA
changed much since do do you still have
within do you understand how do they
operate differently now yeah they
operate much differently um it's much
more
um it's a much deadlier place now for a
couple of
reasons I've been out I've been out for
20 years but I have friends who are
still there um you know after 9911 I was
only around at the agency for another
two and a half three years after 911 but
the agency has has become a military
organization it was never a paramilitary
organization before I mean they sort of
dabbled in that during the vetnam war
but it was essentially well I'll tell
you what the deputy director told me one
time he said you know the mission of the
agency is incredibly simple it is to
recruit spies to steal secrets and to
analyze those secrets to give policy
makers the best informed policy options
available it's really that
simple it was that simple until
September 11th 2001 and now the CIA has
you know entire divisions of people
whose job it is to operate fleets of
deadly drones to
manage kidnapping and rendition teams to
manage assassination teams to work with
um foreign liaison uh or organizations
to kidnap to to kill in some cases uh to
interrogate people who have never been
charged with any crime I mean we can I I
can give you a dozen different examples
some of them are famous like Mahar arar
for example Mahar arar was a uh
political science professor at the
University of
Toronto he was a uh he was ethnically
Syrian but he's he's a Canadian citizen
and um he went to Syria to visit some
relatives of his and then was flying
back to Toronto well you can't fly from
Damascus to Toronto you have to fly
through JFK at least you did back then
and
um and the CIA asked the FBI to pluck
him off the plane which the FBI did and
then the CIA sent him directly back to
Damascus again to undergo nine months of
merciless
torture um they um they they beat him
they uh attached electrodes to his to
his genitals and electrocuted him um
they they did everything you can imagine
them doing to a person in order to break
him and to turn him into just jelly and
at the end of nine months the syrians
came to us and said listen we think this
is the wrong
guy which of course he was the wrong guy
a freaking political science professor
at the UN of Toronto well in the
meantime his wife's waiting for him at
the airport and he never gets off the
plane so she goes to the airline and
they said oh no no he wasn't on the
plane okay well he hasn't called he
didn't call to say he missed his plane
he just never shows up and nobody knows
anything nobody has any idea where he is
well as it turns
out just before the plane landed at JFK
you know how the the flight attendants
will walk through walk up and down the
aisles holding
dutyfree uh brochures he bought a pair
of sunglasses on the plane so a month
after he was supposed to have returned
home his wife gets the credit card
statement in the mail and it shows that
he bought the sunglasses on the plane
and she went to her Member of Parliament
in Canada and said they're lying to me
he was on the
plane so the Canadians went to the went
to the FBI and they they said listen
what's going on and then the FBI said
well you're going to need to talk to the
CIA about
that so finally he was
released and he filed a lawsuit against
uh the US government and the Canadian
government the US has a policy never
ever apologizes ever to
anybody and when you see the US
government especially a National
Security Agency like the
CIA you go to the courtroom and the CIA
walks in and they say say your honor
National Security and the judge says
case
dismissed and that's what happened so he
ended up getting a settlement of $6
million from the Canadian government but
I talked to mahur not too terribly long
ago and he told me that he suffers from
such terrible PTSD and agoraphobia that
he has not left his house in 14 years he
just can't he falls apart there another
guy khed alas now the the name al-as
means the Egyptian so it's not even
really a family name it's more of a
descriptor there are a million people
named KH Alm okay so KH Al musi is a
green grosser in Germany he has a little
fruits and vegetable
shop and he's married to a German woman
and they're not getting along very well
and they have a fight and he decides he
needs a break he's going to go to
Macedonia and visit his brother who is a
citizen there so he gets on a bus to go
from Germany to Macedonia in the
meantime the CIA gets some intelligence
from a sister agency that says there's
this Egyptian terrorist named elas the
Egyptian and he's going to blow up the
American Embassy in
Albania so the CIA gets this information
they say huh there's this guy named khed
Alm he's on a bus he's headed toward
Albania or he's headed in that general
direction we go to the serbs we said
grab this guy off the bus he's going to
blow up the American Embassy we grab him
off the bus they turn them over to the
CIA the CIA turns them over to the
Egyptian intelligence service the
Egyptians pull out his fingernails they
electrocute him they beat him they
waterboard him and then they come back
to us and they say listen we think this
is the wrong guy this guy doesn't know
anything [__] D yeah exactly Jesus
[__] Christ let me tell you something
about KH Ali he didn't give two shits
about the United States when he went in
when he came out he had a beard halfway
down his chest and he's clutching a copy
of the Quran and all he wanted to do was
kill Americans
that's what happens when you do stupid
[__] like
this yes yes I mean and torture itself
like it's been documented like in the
Reservoir Dogs he says you could torture
him all you want he'll tell you he
started the Great Chicago Fire it
doesn't [__] work and you know the
story with abuaba right you you guys at
the time they tortured the [__] out of
this guy he ended up making up stuff
didn't he he made up stuff from like
movies sure you know we used to say
listen he's going to admit to kidnapping
the Lindberg baby at the rate we're
going he'll tell you literally anything
that he thinks you want to hear just to
get you to stop torturing him it's as
simple as that and then look at it this
way
too even if they do tell you the
truth and they they probably will at
least they'll tell you elements of the
truth during torture there's so much
garbage in there that they're telling
you to get you to stop that it's going
to take teams of analysts 6 months to
get through all this trash just to get
to the truth and by then you know the
attack you were hoping to disrupt or the
bomb that you were hoping to to diffuse
it's already too
late yeah yeah yeah and keep it in mind
that the CIA was an organization that
originally started the MK Ultra project
because they were quite positive that
the Soviets had acquired magical te
telekinetic abilities and that they had
to quickly uh match the thing if 70 60
70% of the American public believe in
angels you can bet some of those PE
delusional people work for government in
these higher positions there's nothing
more frightening than a human being I
swear to God John uh um so so I don't
know last time we talked you were you
were you've been on Sputnik news now and
I put you the the link in my description
and you
completely uh shut me down got me in
trouble couple strikes on my account
just for telling them where you could be
found and um is is what's the deal with
the information Warfare these days I
mean it's like obviously the social
media companies are doing the bidding of
whatever political part both both
political parties but a lot of the
Democrat the Twitter files was a big
thing um right but also like fake
accounts doing fake stuff have you
noticed this have you heard anything
about this I mean you have NE trolls the
North American fellow organization which
is like Pro
Ukraine what have you
heard yeah there are a lot of new or
newish organizations out there that have
very important people on their Boards of
Directors for example um who have taken
upon themselves to determine what
Outlets are giving you the truth and
what Outlets are not giving you the
truth you know even the Pentagon for
example is subscribed to some of these
organizations where you get a green
check or a red X when you type the URL
into uh into the browser it's kind of
crazy but uh but yeah you know YouTube
and Twitter and Facebook and Instagram
and really almost all of them except
Telegram and Rumble have stricken us
from um from their platforms we we went
on my show in particular you know it's
it's just a curent event show and it's
just me and an American um co-host who
uh talk about the news of the day we
went from 35 to 38,000 downloads a day
to 1,500 downloads a day which is a good
day like wow 1,200 to 1500 yeah and you
know just to give you an idea how silly
this gets too I had a a weekly 30 minute
segment called criminal Injustice
criminal Criminal Justice Reform is very
important to me as you might guess so
every Thursday I would do 30 minutes
with a guy named Paul Wright who is the
founder of the human rights defense
center in Florida and the publisher of
prison legal news
magazine so every Thursday for 30
minutes we would talk about crooked cops
crooked prosecutors crooked judges uh 14
people in Texas last year dying of heat
stroke in prisons because they refused
to air condition them stuff like that
well The Washington Post assigned a
reporter to listen to the show one day
and the reporter finally published in
the post that sure everything I said was
true but I said it on a Russian Network
and by saying it on a Russian Network
get this I was weakening our
democracy okay it's not the Crooked
judges for example in Pennsylvania Who
Sold children
to these to these Kitty jails right it's
not the Crooked for cash yeah yeah kids
for cash Scandal exactly in Pennsylvania
it's not the Crooked uh prosecutors who
withheld exculpatory evidence or Brady
material in order to run their their
conviction numbers up I was the one who
was weakening our democracy by reporting
it yeah that's what on you John I know
right we're kind of American am I dude
Putin could say the sky was blue and
then if you agreed with him you would be
spreading Russian
disinformation this is true yes and I'll
tell you one of the things it's about
Sputnik you know Sputnik offered
me spudnik offered me a show in
201 16 and I turned it down because I
didn't want to work for the
Russians and then they came back in 2017
and they offered me a show again and I
said well I don't know I said listen if
I were to to accept a show I would want
guarantees that I could say anything I
wanted and I could criticize anyone I
wanted including Vladimir Putin and the
DC bureau chief said done and I said
really I said are you willing to put
that in writing put that in the contract
he said done and he
did and so I say anything I want now
I've been there for seven years no one
has ever asked me to say something or
told me that I couldn't say something
I'll give you an example do you remember
a couple of years ago this uh ethnic
Russian guy and his daughter were
poisoned in York England with
Novak this poison whatever it was
residue or whatever so my co-host at the
time he's like you know we we shouldn't
jump to conclusions it could have been
the ukrainians it could have been the
the Russian mob and I said it was the
KGB or whatever they're calling
themselves today this is what they do
they poison
people right let's just call a spade a
spade the Russians didn't care nobody
objected to it I wasn't suspended or
fired nobody even mentioned it to me you
know because that's the deal I can say
anything I want yeah I heard a colleague
of yours somebody who called into the
show they said you know Putin is a
monster blah blah blah I was like wow
he's on this Russia Network and he can
say this openly this
is totally against the narrative that
Russian is so you know they're so
constrictive and stuff but in the United
States we're so free and yet you know
most of our media is owned by like three
people in their family yeah that's right
it's become a big joke so we're both
chronicling on your show you're
chronicling the the decline of Western
civilization in real time I I do the
same I do a weekly show where it's like
this week in Decline um and there's
nothing we can do to stop it it's we're
just sitting here watching a slow motion
train wreck you know isn't that the
truth you know we've got this uni party
is that with with two candidates and
it's like seriously this is the best we
can do an 81y old and a 77 year old
screaming at each other this is the best
we can do shame on us you know I'll tell
you a funny thing too in the 2020
campaign yeah I I used to be a Democrat
I I quit the Democratic party in
2012 um because it's not a progressive
party it's it's a it's a right of Center
party and if I want to be right of
Center then you know what's the
difference between the Democrats and the
Republicans but anyway um it became
apparent I'm sure you'll recall um that
that Joe Biden was going to be the
and so I I started paying closer
attention I'm a political junkie anyway
so I was paying attention but I paid
even closer attention well you might
remember in one of the debates one of
the primary debates Biden is talking and
his teeth fell out like his Dentures
just
fell he had to catch them and put them
back in his mouth I'm like
seriously and then he was doing a debate
in Iowa and his eyeball started bleed
you know how sometimes the white of your
eye turns all red usually from high
blood pressure his eyeball starts to
bleed and then the week before the Iowa
caucus he goes he goes out on stage to
give a speech and the lights are really
bright and people are chanting we want
Joe we want Joe he was confused because
he couldn't see from the lights where
everybody was he gave his entire speech
with his back to the audience
his entire spee it's all on it's all on
YouTube and and that was that was four
and a half years ago it's only worse now
oh
man awful yeah I just geriatric cobbled
together like a Frankenstein monster
probably pumped full of Narcotics to get
him to stand upright and go out on the
stage Mitch McConnell also just this
geriatric tortoise who can hardly know
he's he needs to retire it's Feinstein
till the last minute they're like buing
her in like a museum exhibit here yeah
she couldn't
even wax museum yeah in her last couple
of weeks uh in office she she tried to
cast a vote against her own Amendment
and they had to correct it because she
was so demented she didn't even know
what she was doing Mitch McConnell every
time he stands up in front of a
microphone he has a mini stroke like
what's that all
about one time when I was in college I
went to a congressional hearing I went
to a senate hearing and um and STM
Thurman was uh was the chairman of the
Senate Judiciary Committee and he pulled
a sandwich out of his pocket and started
eating a
sandwich and Bob Dole's like Mr chairman
Mr chairman Mr chairman like to get him
to put the sandwich back in his pocket
seriously what is this when Bob Dole has
to tell you something you know you [__]
know right
oh my
God Bob do doesn't like that Bob do Bob
do Bob do who ate Bob Do's peanut butter
Bob
do yeah and and somehow we you start
longing for the days of like th those
times because of how ludicrous it is now
I remember seeing George W bush I was
like oh this guy he's not as bad as
where we right right I remember him W ah
exactly that's wrong some kind of [__]
up Stockholm syndrome you've got from
you know glorifying the past but
um um yeah well look come back and do
this again John I I love talking with
you and everybody tune into your show I
can't tell them where it is because I'll
be crucified the but he's on
Rumble who's on Rumble what political
Misfits on Rumble yes yeah uh my dude
hell of a human being uh stick around
we'll talk right after this we'll sign
off to everybody in TV
Land bye everybody